<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Event &#8211; ShoutingFire</title>
	<atom:link href="https://shoutingfire.com/feed/?post_type=event" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://shoutingfire.com</link>
	<description>Global Burner Radio Network</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 05:32:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://shoutingfire.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/cropped-sf-n-logo-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Event &#8211; ShoutingFire</title>
	<link>https://shoutingfire.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Live from Critical Northwest</title>
		<link>https://shoutingfire.com/event/live-from-critical-northwest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[burnbrite]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 01:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://shoutingfire.com/?post_type=event&#038;p=8873</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tuesday July 15th &#8211; 1pm to 4pm PT Brought to you by DJ Leenerella, live at the Critical Northwest event. This live event will be broadcast by DJ Leenerella of Kaleidoscope Mixtape (broadcast on shoutingfire.com) Critical NW is an official Burning Man regional event, sponsored by Ignition Northwest. Come join us for a week-long camping [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3><strong class="html-strong xdj266r x14z9mp xat24cr x1lziwak xexx8yu xyri2b x18d9i69 x1c1uobl x1hl2dhg x16tdsg8 x1vvkbs x1s688f">Tuesday July 15th &#8211; 1pm to 4pm PT</strong></h3>
<p><strong>Brought to you by DJ Leenerella, live at the Critical Northwest event.</strong></p>
<p>This live event will be broadcast by DJ Leenerella of Kaleidoscope Mixtape (broadcast on shoutingfire.com)</p>
<blockquote>
<div class="uvc-main-heading ult-responsive" data-ultimate-target=".uvc-heading.ultimate-heading-1043686dc478cbc7b h2" data-responsive-json-new="{&quot;font-size&quot;:&quot;desktop:26px;&quot;,&quot;line-height&quot;:&quot;desktop:36px;&quot;}">
<h2>Critical NW is an official Burning Man regional event, sponsored by Ignition Northwest.</h2>
</div>
<div class="uvc-sub-heading ult-responsive" data-ultimate-target=".uvc-heading.ultimate-heading-1043686dc478cbc7b .uvc-sub-heading " data-responsive-json-new="{&quot;font-size&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;line-height&quot;:&quot;desktop:26px;&quot;}">
<h4>Come join us for a week-long camping event that brings the principles of Burning Man to Granite Falls in the Pacific Northwest. Every summer we gather together to embrace the spirit and vision of the playa as we build something new right here in the woods and mountains of home.</h4>
<h4></h4>
<h4>The theme this year, <em>Community Garden</em>, helps us plant the seeds of resilience through the cultivation of connection and creativity.</h4>
<h4>Rooted in the principles of Communal Effort and Radical Inclusion, we gather to support and enrich one another with our unique strengths and talents.</h4>
<h4>Together we bloom into a vibrant community, where each individual’s contribution helps us flourish as a whole.&#8221;</h4>
</div>
</blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lakes of Fire (Michigan)</title>
		<link>https://shoutingfire.com/event/lakes-of-fire-michigan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[burnbrite]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 14:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://shoutingfire.com/?post_type=event&#038;p=7169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Live streaming from the event via Radio SGC. &#160; July 16th to the 20th Lakes of Fire is the Great Lakes Region’s official Burning Man Regional Event and is conducted in accordance with the 10 Principles. Come join us as BenmeR and the RadioSGC crew return for their 24/7 broadcast of this yearly collaborative celebration [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Live streaming from the event via Radio SGC.</h1>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2 class="elementor-heading-title elementor-size-default">July 16th to the 20th</h2>
<p>Lakes of Fire is the Great Lakes Region’s official Burning Man Regional Event and is conducted in accordance with the 10 Principles.</p>
<p>Come join us as BenmeR and the RadioSGC crew return for their 24/7 broadcast of this yearly collaborative celebration of art and community, steeped in friendship, fire, and wonder. This community event is both for you and by you – your creativity, your art, and your relentless enthusiasm fuel a life-altering week that many consider “coming home”.</p>
<p>Your Lucky Lake home hosts theme camps as well as open camping; however you join us, you’ll find music, art, and fiery fun – a creative carnival that is built, destroyed, and carefully wiped clean of the earth just once a year.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Radio SCG<a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1s7P53DrXv9dxK4Y-TaoqMHVDPzNGvyCC/view?usp=drive_link"> broadcast schedule from Lakes of Fire is here</a> (all times on schedule are Eastern).</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
